[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the traditional Chinese delicacy shark fin soup contain in high quantities which may cause sterility in men?", "correct_answer": "Mercury", "incorrect_answers": ["Tin", "Sulfur", "Lead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1961 movie West Side Story was base on this play by William Shakespeare.", "correct_answer": "Romeo and Juliet", "incorrect_answers": ["A Midsummer Nights Dream", "Othello", "Much Ado About Nothing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actors Anthony Michael-Hall and Molly Ringwald were dating during the filming of the 1985 classic comedy movie The Breakfast Club.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of the nutria?", "correct_answer": "Large orange teeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Webbed front feet", "Huge black eyes", "Flat beaver like tale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did Americas military actions in Korea first begin?", "correct_answer": "1871", "incorrect_answers": ["1951", "1950", "1958"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the Moon formed?", "correct_answer": "About 4.5 billion years ago", "incorrect_answers": ["About 5.7 billion years ago", "About 300,000 years ago", "About 1 billion years ago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color xanadu is a shade of this color.", "correct_answer": "Grey", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Yellow", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Luiz Bispo built a floating house for about $170. How is his house able to float?", "correct_answer": "It is made out of recycles plastic bottles.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is made out of recycled cigars and cigarettes.", "It is made out of recycled tires.", "It recycles carbon dioxide throughout  the house, making it buoyant."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the female protagonists best friend in Sleepless in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "Rosie ODonnell", "incorrect_answers": ["Rita Wilson", "Parker Posey", "Penny Marshall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the missing number in the following sequence: 11, 16, 32, ___, 74, 79, 158.", "correct_answer": "37", "incorrect_answers": ["64", "38", "69"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did alchemists associate the planets with?", "correct_answer": "Metals", "incorrect_answers": ["Women", "Animals", "Dreams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the light trucks the Opel company began making in 1930?", "correct_answer": "Blitz", "incorrect_answers": ["Man", "Magirus", "Daimler"]}]